<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataProvider on Testing, Automation, Programming and Latest Technology Articles</title>
    <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/tags/dataprovider/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataProvider on Testing, Automation, Programming and Latest Technology Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan Garia)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan Garia)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.pawangaria.com/tags/dataprovider/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Limit certain Test Iterations in TestNG @DataProvider</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testng/limit-certain-test-iterations-in-testng-dataprovider/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan Garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testng/limit-certain-test-iterations-in-testng-dataprovider/</guid>
      <description>Recently while working on one of the projects we were required to limit the number of data set provided from the TestNG DataProvider and Run for example only the first 10 Testcases and skip all others to quick run the @Test. As we are using the TestNG @DataProvider to send the Test Data and the count of the Test Data set provided from the Data Provider is generally more than 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Automated TestNG @Test with @DataProvider Results in TestRail</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/automation/integrate-automated-testng-test-with-dataprovider-results-in-testrail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan Garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/automation/integrate-automated-testng-test-with-dataprovider-results-in-testrail/</guid>
      <description>I saw multiple people are struggling to integrate the TestNG Tests with the TestRail and it becomes even more complex when we start using the @DataProvides in TestNG and then update the Results in the TestRail. So I decided to write and create a step by step complete guide with an example of how we can use @DataProvider and normal @Test and update the results using the TestNG Listeners. As we all know the TestRail is a web-based test case management software to store, manage, track &amp;amp; run test cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use DataProvider in TestNG?</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testng/how-to-use-dataprovider-in-testng/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan Garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testng/how-to-use-dataprovider-in-testng/</guid>
      <description>There are multiple cases, when we have to validate our use-cases where the logic should be same but the test data is different and we must validate our logic for multiple parameters. TestNG provides a very easy way of passing parameters using the DataProvider. In this article we are going to learn how to use DataProvider with @Test.
 A Data Provider is a method on your class that returns an array of array of objects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>